bandera
бандера
that no no this is nonsense, look find
что нет нет это брехня смотрим найди
nowhere I don’t have anything near the ring so
нигде не мне у ринга ничего нет нету так
yours blew up the sun so this is nonsense you are
вашим подорвал солнце так это бред ты
talking with
говоришь с
inside al load this time
внутри аль нагрузку это время
8 now the phone or sho googled
8 сейчас телефон или шо погугли вот
tell me where in what battle or where did you
скажи где в какой там битве или где вы
fight for the panther  the Nazi is real, I'll
пантера воевал за нацист вот реально я
wait,
подожду
it became interesting,
интересно стало
Lord,
господи
where are you near Moscow near the Kursk Bulge,
где это вы под москвой под курской дугой
where, in short,
где и короче нам на колчаковских фронтах
dora fought for the Nazis
дора воевал за нацистов
Bondarev on the Kolchak fronts, he didn’t fight at the
бондарева он не воевал у
UN stop stop feed you were just a stepping
оон стоп стоп подачи ты только шаговый
girl panther fought for the Nazis and
девушка пантера воевал за нацистам а
now such a chicken fought  and killed
теперь уж такая курица воевал и убивал
hello, check tell me where he fought
привет вот проверь скажи где он воевал
bubble
bubble
and
а
what is this war some kind and Misha
что такое эта война какая-то и миша
let's hold
давай держи меня 6 интересно
me  now you will go porsche
кстати сейчас вы отправитесь porsche
will say about the Bandera
скажет про бандеровцы
expense process benefit issued an appeal to
расход процессе пользу издала призыв ко
all of us analysis of the mind
всем нас анализ ума
support in western ukraine
опора на западной украине
nezhin ta  m there was something a
нежин там бывал что-то
lot of text a
много текста
knife there nancy the virgin shaft of Bandera’s
нож там нэнси девой вал бандера
decrees of the cic are sharper than
постановы цик острее
what spots
какой пятен
can be
можно
smeared by a pilot on beams to tankers, it’s
мажем летчиком балки танкистам
very interesting now
аж самому интересно сейчас
that they’ve googled the samples where the panda fought
пробы загугли где воевал панда
what then that is and what it turns out you were about
что тогда то есть и что и получается ты
three or four minutes ago he
минут три или четыре назад сашу он
fought for Sasha  Nazi with such confidence
воевал за нацист с такой уверенностью
m92 I will help you find I will also
м92 я тебе помогу найти я тоже буду
look for where Bandera fought
искать где воевал бандера
hours let's first start the flow
часов давай давай сначала начнем проток
do alpen terra
делаем alpen terra
[music]
[музыка]
let's go so low you now you now
давай так низко ты сейчас ты сейчас
say a lot look here tell me exactly
много скажи смотри вот скажи конкретно
where you fought 2x started let's start with where you fought
где воевал 2x начал начнем с где воевал
or  still admit that he didn’t fight
или все-таки признать что он не воевал
under very big stop the mandarin not
под очень большие stop the mandarin не
my luck and look you said that
моего удачи и смотри ты сказал что
Bandera fought for the Nazis so
бандера воевал за нацистов так
it turns out and now I think he didn’t fight he
оказывается а теперь вешу он не воевал
sat out so he didn’t fight like
отсиживался так то он не воевал как
that let’s start like that he didn’t fight so
то давай так начнется он не воевал так
you  you admit you were mistaken and
ты признаешься ты ошибся и
Bandera did not fight for the Nazis, so
бандера не воевал за нацистов так
that is, you started first, you admit that
то есть начал первым ты признаешь что
Bandera did not fight for the Nazis, this forest
бандера не воевал за нациста этот лес
accidentally said somewhere not  having climbed the
случайно где-то сказал не разобравшись
filing 100 all that again you clearly
подачи 100 все что еще раз ты четко
said that Bandera fought for the Nazis I
сказал что бандера воевал за нацист я
asked I asked I asked for
попросил я попросил я попросил
evidence it is important it is not important
доказательств это это важно не это важно
it is important you searched for five minutes and did not find
это важно ты искал пять минут и не нашел
where he fought, that is, you admit he did not
где он воевал то есть ты признаешь он не
fight for the Nazis like that  let's start with this,
воевал за нацистов так начнем с этого
setting fire to the substitution, here are the words Bender
поджигая подмена вот слова воевал бендер
fought fought for the Nazi or did not fight show
воевал за нациста или не воевал покажи
an example where Bandera fought for the Nazi for
пример где бандера воевал за нацист
at least an hour look for he didn’t fight for the dentist
хоть час искать он не воевал за дантист
drag Bandera’s funds with a cry
потащить бандеровский средства с криком
ignite the feed we will manage this one and now
поджиг подачи сумеем этот этот и сейчас
you now want it just you now
ты сейчас хочешь чтобы просто ты сейчас
want  just to somehow somehow
хочешь просто чтобы как то как то
save your face you want to save
сохранить свое лицо ты хочешь сохранить
face don’t look say tell say won’t eat
лицо не смотри ни скажи скажи не съест
say where you are where are my shaft bender where
выскажи где вы где мои вал бендер где
did bender fight bandera
воевал бендер бандера
bender fought or didn’t fight
бендер воевал или не воевал
what year
каком году
eighteenth for whom you
восемнадцатом за кого
look in what eighteenth year this
смотришь в каком восемнадцатом году этом
civil war yes  and
гражданскую войну да а
how old Bandera was in the eighteenth
сколько лет бандере было в восемнадцатом
year of the mouth, take Bandera's birthday,
году рот возьми день рождения бандеры
come on,
ну давай
he was born on January 1, nine hundred virgins
он родился 1 января девятьсот девятого
in the eighteenth year he was nine
года восемнадцатом году ему было девять
years old against whom and for whom he fought at the
лет против кого и за кого он воевал в 9
age of 9
лет
it was he who was one of all Ukrainians world
именно он был одним всех украинцев world
Ukrainian defense but what difference does it make
защита украинском да какая разница
and childhood you are considered interesting
и детстве тебе считаюсь интересно
Lenin's Habsburgs
габсбургов ленина
there letters if Russians then stick
там буквы если русские то пристать
Habsburgs and capsules
габсбургов и капсул
wanted in the eighteenth year
хотел восемнадцатом году
the village is like this, you don’t know it, so this game to
село так ты это не знаю так вот эту дичь
scoop
черпать
it up on which site read it now,
это вообще на каком сайте читай сейчас
well, I also discovered the Russian
ну вот я тоже википедии открыл русскую
wikipedia Stepan Andreevich Panther there, so I don’t
там пантера степан андреевич так я не
really see where the pipe is written like in the
вижу реально где дудку написано типа
eighteenth year he fought,
восемнадцатом году он воевал
then he gets it, he didn’t fight, then it’s
то получает он не воевал то у
good  madara him loki
хорошо мадара него локи